earnparttimejobs.com 2019-04-24

# Earn:// Part Tme Jobs - Work online from Home - Privacy - privacy

EarnPartTimeJobs.com is totally committed to protecting the privacy of our site visitors and mambers. The EarnPartTimeJobs team members are mambers themselves of other Internet sites and fully appreciate and respect the importance of privacy on the Internet. We will not disclose information about our customers to third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you.

**Your Consent**

We will not sell your name, address, e-mail address, credit card information or personal information to any third party (excluding partners from whom you may have linked to our site) without your permission. 

**Communication & Marketing**

If you have registered as a member we may occasionally update you on services, news and special offers via e-mail, post & telephone. You will be given the opportunity to receive such communications from us and selected third parties when you become a member of EarnPartTimeJobs. 

All EarnPartTimeJobs members have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties. If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us and/or selected third parties you should opt-out by using the "Unsubscribe" link in the email comminication sent to you. 

**What are Cookies?**

A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. If you have registered with us then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit EarnPartTimeJobs, by remembering your email address and/or country for you. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent. 

**Site Statistics**

We may disclose aggregate, anonymised statistics about the number of visitors to this Website or number of members as required by our investors. We use an independent measurement and research company to gather data regarding the visitors to this Website on our behalf using cookies and code which is embedded in the site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. EarnPartTimeJobs uses and stores this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help it improve the services to its users. Further information regarding the way in which this information is obtained and used can be obtained by contacting us.

**Disclosures of your information**

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group of companies. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties: 

  * in the event that EarnPartTimeJobs sells or buys any business or assets; 
  * if EarnPartTimeJobs or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data which we hold about our customers may be one of the transferred assets; or 
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of EarnPartTimeJobs, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Third party sites**

Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

**Checking your Details**

If you wish to verify the details you have submitted to EarnPartTimeJobs you may do so by contacting us. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information. This proof of identity will take the form of your e-mail address and password submitted upon registration. You must therefore keep this information safe as you will be responsible for any action which we take in response to a request from someone using your e-mail and password. We would strongly recommend that you do not use the browser's password memory function as that would permit other people using your terminal to access your personal information. 

**Opting out or erasing your account**

If you wish to opt out of receiving our newsletters, you may do so via the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any newsletter.  
If you want to entirely erase your account wiht us and all your information, you can do so through the "Edit profile" option on your account management page.

**GDPR (Applicable to EU residents)**

For the purposes of applicable EU data protection law (including the General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (the “ **GDPR** ”), we are a ‘data controller’ of your personal information.

You are also entitled to ask us to port your personal information (i.e. to transfer in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, to you), to erase it, or restrict its processing. You also have rights to object to some processing that is based on our legitimate interests, such as profiling that we perform for the purposes of direct marketing, and, where we have asked for your consent to process your data, to withdraw this consent as more fully described below.

These rights are limited in some situations – for example, we can demonstrate that we have a legal requirement to process your personal information. In some instances, this means that we may retain some data even if you withdraw your consent.

Where we require your personal information to comply with legal or contractual obligations, then provision of such data is mandatory: if such data is not provided, then we will not be able to manage our contractual relationship with you, or to meet obligations placed on us. In all other cases, provision of requested personal information is optional.

If you have unresolved concerns you also have the right to complain to data protection authorities. The relevant data protection authority will be the data protection authority of the country: (i) of your habitual residence; (ii) of your place of work; or (iii) in which you consider the alleged infringement has occurred.
